axisrooms.com 2019-04-09

# AxisRooms | Privacy Policy

We, [www.axisrooms.com](http://www.axisrooms.com/), the creator of this Privacy Policy ensure our firm commitment to your privacy vis-à-vis the protection of your priceless information. In order to endow you with our uninterrupted use of services, we may collect and, in some circumstances, disclose information about you. To enhance better protection of your privacy we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, you should contact our Customer Support Desk at [support@axisrooms.com](mailto:support@axisrooms.com)

**1\. OVERVIEW**

We commit to respecting your online privacy data. We further recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) you share with us. Information that are considered personal about you by us includes, but is not limited to, your name, address, email address or other contact information.

In order to use this website, you are required to register yourself by providing the following information which includes, but is not limited to:

(1) Name

(2) User name

(3) Password

(4) Mobile number etc

This privacy policy also applies to data we collect from users who are not registered as members of this site, including, but not limited to, browsing behavior, pages viewed etc.

**2\. NOTIFICATION OF MODIFICATIONS AND CHANGES TO THE T &C AND PRIVACY POLICY**

We reserve the right to change the Terms and Privacy Policy from time to time as seen fit, without any intimation to you, and your continued use of the site will signify your acceptance of any amendment to these terms.

You are therefore advised to re-read the Terms of Service on a regular basis. Should it be that you do not accept any of the modifications or amendments to the Terms, you may terminate your use of this website immediately.

**3\. INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

Our site’s online requisition form requires users to give us contact information (like your name, address, telephone number and email address), and demographic information (like your zip code/pin code). As a [www.axisrooms.com](http://www.axisrooms.com/) member you are required to provide a valid email address at registration and choose a username or alias that represents your identity on our website. Certain information, such as your name, e-mail addresses, is collected in order to, among other things, verify your identity and for use as account numbers in our record system. Email addresses, Geolocations, Intellectual Property, listings viewed, any information entered in the contact us form or any other form displayed on any section of the website are also collected.

**4\. COOKIES**

We use data collection devices such as “cookies” on certain pages of our Websites. “Cookies” are small files sited on your hard drive that assist us in providing customized services. We also offer certain features that are only available through the use of a “cookie”. Cookies can also help us provide information, which is targeted to your interests. Cookies may be used whether you register with us or not.

**5\. EXTERNAL LINKS ON WEBSITE**

You are a restricted user of this website.  
The Website may include hyperlinks to other web sites or content or resources. We have no control over any websites or resources, which are provided by companies or persons other than Us.  
You acknowledge and agree that We are not responsible for the availability of any such external sites or resources, and does not endorse any advertising, products or other materials on or available from such websites or resources.  
You acknowledge and agree that We are not liable for any loss or damage which may be incurred by you as a result of the availability of those external sites or resources, or as a result of any reliance placed by you on the completeness, accuracy or existence of any advertising, products or other materials on, or available from, such websites or resources. These third-party service providers and Third-Party Sites may have their own privacy policies governing the storage and retention of your personal information that you may be subject to. We recommend that when you enter a Third-Party Site, you review the Third Party Site’s privacy policy as it relates to safeguarding your personal information. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Website.

**6\. OUR USE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. Finally, we may use your IP address to help protect our partners and ourselves from fraud. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available. We will transfer information about you if We are acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, we will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  
We may release your personal information to a third-party in order comply with a Court Order or other similar legal procedure, or when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law; prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss; or investigate or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or violations of Our  Terms of Use. We may disclose personally identifiable information to parties in compliance with our Copyright Policy as mentioned in the Terms of Use as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. In such events, We may disclose name, address, country, phone number, email address and company name.

**7\. CONFIDENTIALITY**

You further acknowledge that the Website may contain information which is designated confidential by Us and that you shall not disclose such information without our prior written consent.

Your information is regarded as confidential and therefore will not be divulged to any third party, unless if legally required to do so to the appropriate authorities.

We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third party or use your e-mail address for unsolicited mail. Any emails sent by us will only be in connection with the provision of agreed services and products.

**8\. OUR DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION**

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting and foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government, law enforcement agencies or third parties. Under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or members may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from our Websites. Therefore, although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications would always remain private.

As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party.

**8.1 Law and Order:**    We cooperate with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement and other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us or you to legal liability.

**9\. ACCESSING, REVIEWING AND CHANGING YOUR PROFILE**

Following registration, you can review and change the information you submitted except your display name, during registration. If you change any information we may keep track of your old information. You can change your registration information such as: name, address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, and profile.

To remove your profile so that others cannot view it, contact our customer support team at [support@axisrooms.com](mailto:support@axisrooms.com)

We will retain in our files information you have requested to remove for certain circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our terms and conditions. Further, such prior information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored ‘back up’ systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests.

**10\. CONTROL OF YOUR PASSWORD**

When you sign up to become a Member, you will also be asked to choose a password. You are entirely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password. It is important that you protect it against unauthorized access of your account and information by choosing your password carefully, and keeping your password and computer secure by signing out after using our services

You agree not to use the account, username, email address or password of another Member at any time or to disclose your password to any third party. If you choose to share this information with third parties to provide you additional services, you are responsible for all actions taken with your login information and password and therefore should review each third party’s privacy policy. You are responsible for all actions taken with your login information and password, including fees. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. You agree to notify us immediately if you suspect any consistent unauthorized use of your account or access to your password even after changing it.

**11\. OTHER INFORMATION COLLECTORS**

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are on our Websites or on other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. To the extent that we use third party advertisers, they adhere to their own privacy policies. Since we do not control the privacy policies of the third parties, you are subject to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

You agree not to use the account, username, email address or password of another Member at any time or to disclose your password to any third party. If you choose to share this information with third parties to provide you additional services, you are responsible for all actions taken with your login information and password and therefore should review each third party’s privacy policy. You are responsible for all actions taken with your login information and password, including fees. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password. You agree to notify us immediately if you suspect any consistent unauthorized use of your account or access to your password even after changing it.

**12\. SECURITY**

We treat data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by members inside and outside the company. We do not recommend transfer of sensitive information (such as credit card number) and bank account details via the Site. Users are recommended to do so offline, on the phone or via personal emails. Us follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once Us receives it. However, “perfect security” does not exist on the Internet. You therefore agree that any security breaches beyond the control of our standard security procedures are at your sole risk and discretion.

**13\. DISCLAIMER**

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information (including sensitive information like credit card information and bank account number) will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. Therefore, although we are committed to protecting your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information will always remain private. As a user of the Site, you understand and agree that you assume all responsibility and risk for your use of the Site, the internet generally, and the documents you post or access and for your conduct on and off the Site.

**14\. DISPUTES AND JURISDICTION**

All disputes involving but not limited to rights conferred, compensation, refunds, and other claims through this policy will be resolved through a two-step Alternate Dispute Resolution mechanism.

**14.1. Stage 1: Mediation.**  In case of a dispute, the matter will first be attempted to be resolved by a sole mediator who is a neutral third party and will be selected at the mutual acceptance of a proposed mediator by both parties. Both parties may raise a name for sole arbitrator and in the case both parties accept the proposed name, the said person shall be appointed sole mediator. In the case the parties are not able to reach a consensus within two proposed mediators, the Company reserves the right to decide who the final mediator is. The decision of the mediator is not binding on both parties however, the parties in good faith will attempt to bind by the decision.

**14.2. Stage 2: Arbitration.** In the case that mediation does not yield a result suitable or preferred by any one of the parties, arbitration may follow, the award of which is binding on both parties. The Arbitration Board is to comprise three members. One is to be appointed by each party and the third member is to be nominated by the two appointed members by mutual consent between them. The award as the outcome of the arbitration is final and binding on both parties and there shall be no further remedy available to both parties. The arbitration proceedings will take place in the English Language and will be situated in the Bengaluru, Karnataka. The mode of appointment of the arbitrators is as provided above.

If the dispute cannot be resolved by this two-step Alternate Dispute Resolution mechanism, it shall be referred to the courts in Bengaluru, Karnataka.
